## **SUMMARY**

Full-stack developer transitioning from Human Resources. Passionate about creating organizational management products as I enjoy seeing thoughts come to life that are productive, efficient, and effective. Over seven years of administrative experience working collaboratively with different teams and handling multiple priorities at once.

# **SKILLS**

LANGUAGES: Javascript, Ruby, HTML, CSS, SQL

FRAMEWORKS & L: NodeJS, ReactJS, Ajax, Express, EJS, jQuery, Twilio, Rails, Bootstrap, ActiveRecord, SASS, React Redux,

NextJS, Tailwind

SYSTEMS & DATABASES: PostgresSQL, Git

TESTING: Jest, Storybook, Cypress, RSpec, Mocha, Chai

SPOKEN LANGUAGES: Fluent English, Conversational Cantonese, Basic Mandarin

## **PROJECTS**

My Portfolio

Feb. 2023

My portfolio is a client-sided application to display my past projects and showcase my front-end development skills.

Tech Stack: Javascript React NextJS Tailwind

Doable Dec. 2022

A project management application that makes it easy for a user to organize their new projects/tasks.

Tech Stack: React, Bootstrap, NodeJS, Express, Axios, PostgresSQL

Scheduler Nov. 2022

A single page client application that uses React view library where a user can book, edit, or cancel interview appointments.

Tech Stack: React, Axios, Classnames, Normalize, Storybook

## **EDUCATION**

Lighthouse Labs · Sept. 2022 to Dec. 2022

Diploma Full-Stack Web Development

Simon Fraser University · Jan. 2019 to Apr. 2020

Human Resources Management Certificate

University of British Columbia · Sept. 2010 to Apr. 2014

Bachelor of Management 2014

## **EMPLOYMENT**

### **Provincial Health Services Authority**

Labour Relations Coordinator · Nov. 2020 to June 2022 · Vancouver, BC

- Supported the Labour Relations team with letters, grievance responses, reports, minutes and other ad hoc related requests
- SuperUser in Human Resources Solutions: manage all users (new employees/union members, etc.) and grievances, familiar with PeopleSoft to query employee information

#### Bureau Veritas Commodities Canada

Human Resources Assistant · June 2019 to Apr. 2020 · Vancouver

- Provided Human Resources support to the Regional HR Manager for over 300 employees
- Utilized SAP SuccessFactors and ADP WorkForce Now to process all HR-related data